Charis Wan

(021) 0275 1156

27 Beaufort Place
Papatoetoe
Auckland
wnjgon1990@gmail.com

Career Objective

Website designer/developer with technical expertise in developing advanced responsive websites and JC MVC web applications. Strong UI layout, user experience development and compatible responsive front-end development of website designs for different devices, browsers and screen sizes. I also have a natural talent painting skills, gained over 10 years through-put schooling. Good communication and artistic expression skills. Eager to learn and loves working in a team environment.

Areas Of Expertise

Computer and Technical Skills

- Front-end: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, EmberJS, JQuery, AngularJS
- Back-end: PHP, Yii Framework, JSON, C# .NET, JSP
- Database: MS SQL, MySQL
- Testing: Creating Test Plans, UAT Testing
- Graphic Design: Photoshop, Indesign, Illustrator, Fireworks

Professional

- Ability to hand code HTML5/CSS3
- Strong understanding of JavaScript & jQuery
- Proficiency in building websites to web standards
- Proficiency in responsive web design
- Experience in progressive enhancement
- Experience in cross-browser and cross-device testing
- Solid experience in Photoshop, Dreamweaver and Fireworks
- Good understanding of SEO principles
- Experience working with PHP developers

Personal

- High-level logical and creative thinker, positive and optimistic
- Excellent ability to handle time effectively and to prioritize tasks
- Managed team to ensure project completed within deadlines
- Honest, confident and friendly in working with a group or team as well as seeing others' perspectives
- Self-motivated, serious attitude to work and the ability to focus on each project
- Fluent in English and Chinese, basic Japanese

Employment History

Trends Publishing Website Platform

July 2013 - Dec 2014

(HubStar Ltd)

- http://trendsideas.com/ (myTrends Web Application)
- Front-End website/application development
- UX development and responsive CSS development
- Responsive screen development for mobile/tablet devices & browsers
- Good Search Engine Optimization enhancement
- Graphic image slicing and web optimisation
- eCommerce gateway integration function (DPS)

Unitec Health Flip Ebook

July 2012 - March 2013

(Voluntary project)

- Achieve client needs and requests.
- Efficiently complete the tasks in each milestone
- Reasonably manage time to break down the project into different parts
- Discover potential needs to make project widely available to the public

Education History

Bachelor of Computing Systems

July 2010 - June 2013

(United Institute of Technology)

Key Courses Completed:

Internet website design (HTML5, CSS3)(level 7)
 Web application development (ASP, PHP) (level 7)
 Multimedia application development (Flash) (level 7)
 Grade: A
 Grade: A

Projects Completed

"Website User Research Tool" Grade: A

The web research application that can be implemented as a tool for collecting and adopting user information and researcher can collect user result by executing survey to analyse and statistic for calculating the probability value and compare with given formula for validation, which is based on PHP and MYSQL environment for development.

<u>Interests</u>

- Photographic design
- Traveling around the world
- Watching and learning animation skills
- Sports --- playing badminton, tennis and swimming
- Reading books --- science fiction, fantasy novels & detective stories
- Painting ----Sketching, water colour painting, acrylic painting

Referees

Available on request

HubStar Director - Jason Liddiard